<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ModMetaData>
  <name>Westerado Wilderness (Continued)</name>
  <packageId>Mlie.WesteradoWilderness</packageId>
  <author>Soyuz, DanRatherman, and SpiderCamp</author>
  <url>https://github.com/emipa606/WesteradoWilderness</url>
  <supportedVersions>
    <li>1.2</li>
  </supportedVersions>
  <modDependencies>
    <li>
      <packageId>Mlie.Westerado</packageId>
      <displayName>Westerado (Continued)</displayName>
      <steamWorkshopUrl>steam://url/CommunityFilePage/2236973780</steamWorkshopUrl>
      <downloadUrl>https://github.com/emipa606/Westerado/releases/latest</downloadUrl>
    </li>
  </modDependencies>
  <loadAfter>
    <li>Mlie.Westerado</li>
  </loadAfter>
  <description>Update of Soyuz, DanRatherman, and SpiderCamps mod
https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=1613534100

[img]https://i.imgur.com/GYswkZ7.png[/img]

Support-chat:
https://invite.gg/mlie

Non-steam version:
https://github.com/emipa606/WesteradoWilderness
	
--- Original Description ---
Westerado Wilderness aims to alter biomes to achieve a more western-themed feel to the game, whilst trying to maintain the balance of vanilla Rimworld.

Features
Makes alteration to biomes to give the game more of a western theme
10+ New plants; chanterelles, prickly pears, and lavender are a select few of the new plants you'll see
1 New weather; blizzards!
Arid biomes have more arid vegetation, adding to the feel of a desolate, hostile, place; debris-like plants and cacti now rule the arid biomes
Boreal, Forest, and Swamp biomes have a much higher degree of plant and animal life, including mushrooms
Some vanilla plants now have flowering versions of them
Compatibility and minor fixes with/to Snowy Trees by Nandonalt and Tejko
Arid and Cold biomes are now more hostile to settlement!

We're also planning on releasing future content updates!


Got any questions? Ask them in the aptly named Suggestions Thread and we'll answer them when we can. Got any suggestions? Feel free to post them in the comments, and we'll respond as to the suggestion's feasibility when we can.

Add-ons and Recommended Mods
We suggest using all the add-ons, but none of them are required.
Add-on: Horses by SpiderCamp, adds horses!
Add-on: Westerado Gunslinger, adds compatibility with Combat Extended
Add-on: Westerado The Gun Jesus Revelations, renames guns to their 'proper' label
Recommended: Snowy Trees by Nandonalt and Tejko, plants get snowy when it snows

Mod loading order
Westerado Wilderness should be loaded after Westerado (Core), if you're using Snowy Trees by Nandonalt and Tejko put that before Westerado (Core). Something like:
Snowy Trees by Nandonalt and Tejko
Westerado
Westerado Wilderness
Westerado Gunslinger
Westerado The Gun Jesus Revelations

Compatibility
Should be compatible with anything that Westerado (Core) is compatible with. Things that could cause problems:
Mods that radically change vanilla biomes

Have you found a compatibility issue? Please inform us in the comments and we'll try to patch it when we can! Make sure to include a list of mods you've used and any potential error messages.


Soyuz - XML, Artwork
DanRatherman - Artwork
SpiderCamp - Artwork

Some Art from SpiderCamp's Decorative Plants mod

Inspired by:
Fertile Planet by Makaru
Increased Forest Density by Helpful Bot
Snowy Trees by Nandonalt and Tejko

Licensing
All original content (e.g. text, imagery, sounds) in this mod is licensed under the CC-BY-SA 4.0 license</description>
</ModMetaData>